apexarticlebase.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy policy

  **  1.** ApexArticleBase.com respects the privacy of its users and does not collect any personally identifiable user information without prior notice. Web statistics are the sole and private property of ApexArticleBase.com and are only used for troubleshooting purposes.  
   **2.** ApexArticleBase.com generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. When you register to become a member of ApexArticleBase.com and subscribe to our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name and/or other information.  
  **  3.** ApexArticleBase.com uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our newspapers, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice  
   **4.** We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.  
 **    5\. **We may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those ervices. ApexArticleBase.com does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.  
  **  6\. **ApexArticleBase.com may use cookies to keep some information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies.  
  **  7.** **** Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.  
   **8.** If you don't want cookies stored on your computers, your Web browser would likely include an option that allows you to not accept cookies. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of ApexArticleBase.com may not function properly.  
   **9.** While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.  
  **10.** ApexArticleBase.com is not intended for use by minors or children, especially those under age 18. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and/or chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardians(s) before using our services, including registration and/or subscriptions to our services offered by this site.  
  **11.** If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. ApexArticleBase.com cannot be held responsible for any action by your children while using our services, with or without your consents.  
  **12.** This is the website of ApexArticleBase.com. We can be reached via e-mail "at"apexarticlebase"at"gmail.com. The email address has been encoded as such for security reason. Please replace "at" with @.  
  **13.** This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time without any prior notice to the visitors. Continued access of   
ApexArticleBase.com by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. It is the goal of ApexArticleBase.com to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

**Additionally:** Privacy Policy for ApexArticleBase.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at *EMAIL*.

At ApexArticleBase.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by ApexArticleBase.com  and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, ApexArticleBase.com  makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

ApexArticleBase.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following

.:: URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......

Google Adsense

Commission Junction

Clickbank

Azoogle

Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ApexArticleBase.com  send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ApexArticleBase.com  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ApexArticleBase.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

ApexArticleBase.com cannot be held responsible for any situations that may arise due to any wording or misunderstanding relating to this Privacy Policy.
